ELLIRAYNA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 647 996 7420

elli@elliraynai.com

636 Danforth Ave, Toronto, M4K1R3

in elliraynai

<u>elliraynai.com</u>

github.com/eraynai

PROFILE

I am a full stack developer with a background in user experience design. My coding journey began with building interactive and engaging experiences in VR/AR. From there I began experimenting with the web, and fell in love with development. I have a passion for building applications and working collaboratively in a team to make the best possible product.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

React

Express

NodeJS

Mongo

Django

PostgreSQL

Python

Vue

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Git

HOBBIES

Fitness

Writing

Drawing

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive Certificate

General Assembly

April 2021 - August 2021

- Was selected as the technical lead for the collaborative projects built in React, Express, and Django
- Was chosen for my ability to stay organized, focused, and willingness to help with all aspects of the project

Interaction Design and Development Advanced Diploma

George Brown College

September 2018 - April 2021

 Built many collaborative projects in different areas of design including web, mobile, and physical installations

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Technologist Intern

No Fixed Address | January 2021 - April 2021

- Sole frontend developer on a campaign for a client utilizing the Vue.js framework
- Consistently performed well under pressure amid tight time constraints and had to learn new development skills during the project
- Conducted market research on different types of technologies that could be utilized by clients

AR Designer

Snap | October 2020 - December 2020

- Participated in the Snap AR residency based on the my pitch for a machine learning experience called 'Nourish'
- Responsible for creative direction, user flows, concept designs, motion capture animation for 3D models, and programming interactions in JavaScript